{
    "id": "a4fa1087ff2f4bb7b0cfb5252fac0504",
    "title": "Enough and too",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a182e218715f4de2803b03c0469dfc27",
            "title": "Enough or Too | Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The coat was ………………… so I didn’t buy it.",
                    "description": "Too means 'more than is required'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too expensive",
                        "enough expensive",
                        "expensive enough"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If the water is ......................, we can go for a swim.",
                    "description": "Enough goes after the adjective or adverb it modifies. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "too warm",
                        "enough warm",
                        "warm enough"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "His theories are …………………. to understand.",
                    "description": "Too shows unwanted extremes. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "too difficult",
                        "difficult enough",
                        "enough difficult"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We didn’t manage to sell ………………….",
                    "description": "When enough modifies a noun, it goes before the noun. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "tickets enough",
                        "enough tickets"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There were ...................... people at the party.",
                    "description": "Too cannot modify a noun however, it can go before words like many or much to indicate numbers or quantity. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ..................... to handle this job.",
                    "description": "Enough goes after the adjective it modifies. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "experienced enough",
                        "enough experienced",
                        "too experienced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ………………… to handle the situation.",
                    "description": "Use 'too' to talk about unwanted or undesirable extremes. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "too immature",
                        "immature enough",
                        "enough immature"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is never ……………….. to start.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "late enough",
                        "enough late",
                        "too late"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is …………………. to have a baby.",
                    "description": "Both ‘too old’ and ‘old enough’ are possible here with different meanings. She is too old to have a baby. (= She cannot have a baby now because she is too old.) / She is old enough to have a baby. (= She is of the right age to have a baby.)",
                    "answers": [
                        "too old",
                        "old enough",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I quit because I had had ..................... their quarreling.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "enough",
                        "enough of",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}